<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Industry's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Greg Harrelson, a top Real Estate Agent in Myrtle Beach, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 11:00:09 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 11:00:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Objection or Question? Knowing the Difference</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/prXT7UK8xCs?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sometimes clients ask their agents questions, but the agents hear them as objections. What&amp;rsquo;s the difference?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a client or a prospect asks a real estate agent a question, the agent needs to be very careful about interpreting it as an objection. Sometimes it’s a knee-jerk reaction to treat someone’s questions that way, but &lt;strong&gt;when you respond to a question as though it were an objection, all you’ve done is create the objection&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example to help illustrate what I mean:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suppose that a prospect was to ask you, “Will you cut your commission fee?” That’s a question, but many agents would hear that as an objection and start listing all the reasons why they can’t or shouldn’t cut the commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, it really was just a question. Instead of framing it as an objection, try giving some response to the effect of, “You know, I’m sorry, but I can’t do that. Do you have any other questions?” That way, you can give them an honest answer and move on to their other queries. &lt;strong&gt;If the question comes up again, then you can start treating it like an objection&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s some roleplay to expound upon my example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;“Will you cut your commission fee?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent&lt;/strong&gt; -  &lt;em&gt;“You know, I’m sorry, but I can’t do that. Do you have any other questions?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;“Well, another agent told me that they would, and that’s one of the things we’re considering when we compare different agents.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I believe that half the time when people ask us these questions, they’re not doing so to raise an objection.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/objection-or-question-knowing-the-difference.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I believe that half the time when people ask us these questions, they’re not doing so to raise an objection.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that last response, you now know that it’s an objection, and you may need to dig a little deeper in order to handle the objection and win over the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my experience, I believe that half the time when people ask us these questions, they’re not doing so to raise an objection. By following the methods that I’ve shared today, you won’t have as many objections to handle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this or other topics, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to hear from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/objection-or-question-knowing-the-difference.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/objection-or-question-knowing-the-difference.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Coaching &amp; How to Find the Right Coach for You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Efa7S4ueiqU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;I believe that every real estate agent should have a coach&amp;mdash;here&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to build and sustain a profitable business, then you need to hire a coach. I believe all real estate agents (and all professionals in any industry) should hire a coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? No matter how well you’re doing, you can still do more with less effort, and this is where a coach can help you. You can be making money, but a coach can make you more profitable. Additionally, people only seem to want to hire a coach when they’re not doing so well, but if you wait until business falters to hire a coach, you have to deal with the challenge of actually paying that coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, with that in mind, here are three tips that will help you hire the right coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;choose a coach who’s walked the walk&lt;/strong&gt;. There are a lot of coaches out there who’re willing to take your money but haven’t actually done the level of business you might already be doing. I know coaches who’ve sold 30 or 40 properties a year with a team of eight people and now they want to educate others on how to build a team. Here’s the thing, though: An eight-man team isn’t profitable only selling 30 to 40 properties a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn from someone who’s experienced and has actually produced at a high level instead of just read a book—coaching from experience is a lot better than coaching from a book. Also, make sure they’ve produced year after year and they’re not a one-hit wonder. In other words, a coach can average 20 deals a year and then all of a sudden reach 70 deals one year, but only because they bought a bunch of Zillow leads. That’s not the kind of coaching you want to look for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, &lt;strong&gt;choose a coach who’s present all the time&lt;/strong&gt;. Think about professional sports teams who practice every day in between their actual games. Their coaches are with them at every practice and on the sidelines during the games. They’re not just watching them on TV. Similarly, you want a coach who’s present all the time instead of someone who’s with you one hour per week and then disappears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=No matter how well you’re doing, you can still do more with less effort, and this is where a coach can help you.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-importance-of-coaching-how-to-find-the-right-coach-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“No matter how well you’re doing, you can still do more with less effort, and this is where a coach can help you.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, &lt;strong&gt;pick somebody who’s willing to tell you what you don’t want to hear when you don’t want to hear it&lt;/strong&gt;. A lot of coaches out there are great cheerleaders, but real growth comes from coaches who hold you accountable and can tell you about things you can do better. Don’t hire a cheerleader. Instead, hire someone who wants to help you develop and wants you to be their next top producer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know it’s hard to find coaching that matches these exact criteria, but when you do, that’s when you’ll find other top producers. These agents surround themselves with a coaching environment that’s constant, and if you want to take your business to the next level, you need to align yourself with coaching companies that provide this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality is, you can’t pay for this type of coaching. Just a weekly 30-minute session alone would cost you $1,000. If you find the right company and align yourself with them, though, you’ll receive their coaching as one of their value adds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have expert advisors in Charleston and Century 21 Vanguard in Columbia, and we have these kinds of coaching programs in place. We coach agents every day on how to grow their business in a profitable manner, so if you’d like to do the same for your business, don’t hesitate to call or email me so we can get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other real estate questions, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-importance-of-coaching-how-to-find-the-right-coach-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-importance-of-coaching-how-to-find-the-right-coach-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drive Eyes to Your Listings in 3 Simple Steps</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OsITGEOw5Tc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a fun, quick challenge for you to complete this Friday. Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to do.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently had an idea that I decided to turn into a challenge. Usually when I challenge you, it’s to take an action that I know is going to bring a big benefit back to you and your business. It’s also usually something that is simple and free. This challenge is no exception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s what I created: The Friday Facebook Challenge&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s very simple and will only take about five minutes. I challenge every one of you to follow this system today:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Take one of your listings or a company listing and post it on your personal Facebook page today&lt;/strong&gt;. Posting to your personal page will ensure that the people we want to attract (your sphere) see the post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Include “Featured listing by (your name) at (company name)” with a link under that line to the listing&lt;/strong&gt;. The branding here is invaluable and will direct traffic to the listing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Keep up with the post throughout the day to see if it has been liked, commented on, or shared&lt;/strong&gt;. If somebody shares the post with someone specific, you can bet they are looking for a home that fits the criteria. The person who shared it with them tips us off to the lead, who you can then reach out to. We have used this strategy and gotten leads, set appointments, and written contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If someone shares the post on Facebook, keep a close eye on the person who they share it with.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/drive-eyes-to-your-listings-in-3-simple-steps.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If someone shares the post on Facebook, keep a close eye on the person who they share it with.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you go. Your Friday Facebook Challenge is quick, simple, free, and effective. It can put you in a great position to get a new lead that you can start working tomorrow. If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/drive-eyes-to-your-listings-in-3-simple-steps.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/drive-eyes-to-your-listings-in-3-simple-steps.html</guid>
        
        <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Are the Biggest Challenges Facing Agents in Today’s Market?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/afljBD7L_CI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeing agents struggle more and more with certain aspects of the real estate business. These are the three problems I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed the most.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m always keeping an eye on the market, so today I want to talk about three of the challenges I see real estate agents facing right now when trying to build their business or break through to the next level:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Being too late to the lead&lt;/strong&gt;. A lot of agents are struggling with the “speed to lead” concept. By the time many agents reach out to a lead, the lead has already spoken to another agent. That’s not a new concept. You already know the challenges that can happen when you don’t have that speed. Could you be throttling your leads based on your availability? If you know you’re going to be out all afternoon, why would you generate leads during that time when you’re not going to be able to reach out quickly? I’m not a proponent of turning your lead flow off, but you do have to ask yourself why would you have them if you can’t use them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Managing consumers’ nurture demands&lt;/strong&gt;. The demands of agents have changed with our consumers. The challenge is that now we’re capturing the lead so much earlier in the process than we used to. It requires a much more longer-term nurture. Instead of being ready to buy in 30 days, they might not be ready for another 18 months. Those leads require two different nurture programs, but not all agents have caught up to that fact yet. When you’re building a nurture campaign these days, you need to make sure they combine multiple avenues (text, call, email, Facebook messages, etc.). You’ll need multiple channels in order to win the attention of leads in today’s real estate world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Anything can work if you give it 100%.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/what-are-the-biggest-challenges-facing-agents-in-todays-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Anything can work if you give it 100%.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Focusing on the one thing that works&lt;/strong&gt;. Just about everything works if you just give it 100% of your effort. Whether you choose to go the open house route, the direct mail route, or the FSBO route, all of these strategies can work, but they won’t all work at the same time. Pick one or two areas and put 100% of your effort in for 90 days at the minimum and you’ll generate tremendous momentum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the three biggest struggles I’m seeing with agents in today’s market. If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I would love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/what-are-the-biggest-challenges-facing-agents-in-todays-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/what-are-the-biggest-challenges-facing-agents-in-todays-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Did We Get 816 Listings in Q1 2019?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dDBEpUSqrkk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Year to date, the Harrelson Group has gotten over 816 listings. How did we do it? Find out right here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just the first quarter of 2019, we had 816 listings, but by the time you read this, the Harrelson Group will probably have well over 900 listings under our belt. But how do we do that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well first, &lt;strong&gt;I may own our brokerage, but I run it like a team&lt;/strong&gt;. Each of our team members is independently building their own business—I just happen to be the coach providing the systems, leads, training, and resources needed to build a business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2018, we began to set goals and make commitments. Our goal was to increase the number of listings taken and improve our inventory levels. So many people were upset about how hard it was to find listings in our low-inventory market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, &lt;strong&gt;we committed to collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;. As a group, we brainstormed tactics for increasing the number of listings we would take and created hundreds of ideas on how we could obtain new listings. Each individual agent then decided which of those ideas they wanted to focus on; some focused on just one tactic, and others focused on executing five or 10 different ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At our office, we have a saying: “Your goal is my goal.” We’re constantly setting goals and working together to help our team members actually achieve those goals, and time has shown that when we help out fellow agents do better in their business, we become better ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Making goals, collaborating, holding each other accountable, and executing strategies are key if you want to grow your listing inventory.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-did-we-get-816-listings-in-q1-2019.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Making goals, collaborating, holding each other accountable, and executing strategies are key if you want to grow your listing inventory.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our team-oriented environment, &lt;strong&gt;we also hold each other accountable&lt;/strong&gt;. When someone creates a big goal to meet, there will always be times when they don’t feel like showing up or taking action on the commitments they made. But on our team, when one agent sees another slipping up, they’ll reach out and prod them on and ask how they can help get them back on track. A team environment pushes everybody to the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, &lt;strong&gt;we took action to actually execute our goals&lt;/strong&gt;. We didn’t just call 5,000 homeowners and get 816 listings—there are so many ways to get listings. Our success is due to our focus on the approach, not on our methods of getting the listings themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making goals, collaborating, holding each other accountable, and executing strategies are key if you want to grow your listing inventory. The challenge that most people have is being all by themselves. On a team, we put our heads together to help each other figure it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow this model of approach and just see what will happen to your business over the next three or four months&lt;/strong&gt;. If you have any questions, feel free to give me a call or send an email. I’d love to talk with you about how to create this type of environment in your own brokerage.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-did-we-get-816-listings-in-q1-2019.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-did-we-get-816-listings-in-q1-2019.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Shouldn’t Care if the Market Shifts—Here’s Why</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/U3pom9Kypxg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you set your business up correctly, you needn&amp;rsquo;t be worried about a market shift. Here are three tips to help you do just that.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a professional agent, should you care if our market shifts?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you set your business up correctly, the answer is no. If anything, a market shift can help you because it will lead to more part-time agents switching careers and leaving a bigger piece of the pie behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t want anybody to suffer because of a downturn, but for some, this is inevitable. If you want to keep your business stable in the face of a market shift, there are three tips you need to follow that will help you focus on helping your clients instead of just surviving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, I’ve timestamped each of these tips and how you can apply them so you can skip ahead in the video above at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2:00 - Go lean&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4:03 - Collaborate&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5:38 - Be active, not passive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Fewer expenses + more ideas + more leads = more business no matter what the market does.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/you-shouldnt-care-if-the-market-shiftsheres-why.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Fewer expenses + more ideas + more leads = more business no matter what the market does.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter what’s going on in your local market, you need to follow these three tips. Another way to think of them is by breaking them down into this simple formula: fewer expenses + more ideas + more leads = more business no matter what the market does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We care very much about putting our clients in the best financial position possible during a market shift, but we shouldn’t have to stress out over our business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to talk more about how to thrive instead of merely survive during a market shift, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/you-shouldnt-care-if-the-market-shiftsheres-why.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/you-shouldnt-care-if-the-market-shiftsheres-why.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 3 Mindsets Choices That Can Boost Your Real Estate Career</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ej7c0tQ5LPo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your attitude, approach, and expectations play a key role in your business. Here&amp;rsquo;s what you should do to keep them positive.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are three things you can change in your mindset that will help you get more out of your real estate business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many distractions and frustrations that come at us throughout each day. How we manage these trials is up to our attitude, approach, and expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a look at your attitude&lt;/strong&gt;. Do you see the glass as half empty or half full? Are things problems or opportunities? Your attitude affects how you view situations, and if you see things as pains and problems, you’re much less likely to want to deal with them. If you take things as challenges that you can solve, you’ll do much better in your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you get a lowball offer—it can be discouraging and may put you in a negative mindset. If you think, “This is never going to work out,” how is that going to affect your approach? Think of it this way: You got an offer, which means you’re better off than when you had none. Then, it’s time to figure out how you can negotiate it into something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Ultimately, your attitude, approach, and expectations will influence your final results.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-3-mindsets-choices-that-can-boost-your-real-estate-career.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Ultimately, your attitude, approach, and expectations will influence your final results.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re feeling discouraged and upset, your approach will reflect that&lt;/strong&gt;. That approach further harms your expectations. If you feel like everything is going to fail, and you act like everything is going to fail, then what are you going to expect of the end result? If you don’t expect a positive outcome, it’ll be hard for your client to expect one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your client will mirror your actions&lt;/strong&gt;. If you’re positive, they’ll stay positive as well, but if you’re negative, they’ll also follow suit. With a negative outlook, deals that could be salvaged are instead being thrown away. Ultimately, your attitude, approach, and expectations will influence your final results. These results are generated from your clients’ feelings, so it’s up to you whether you want the outcome to be good or bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want good results, have a great attitude when it’s difficult. &lt;strong&gt;Things will rarely be perfect, but if you can stay positive through the pain, you will win in the end&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like to talk about building your business, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-3-mindsets-choices-that-can-boost-your-real-estate-career.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-3-mindsets-choices-that-can-boost-your-real-estate-career.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Low-Cost Marketing Techniques You Can Implement</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/O2nT2GLZ-F8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marketing is one of the most important parts of selling a home. Here are some inexpensive, effective techniques that we use for our listings.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure you’ve been in a situation where you’ve talked to a seller client after a few weeks and they want to know what you’ve done to market their home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of times, &lt;strong&gt;sellers think that all an agent does is take a listing, set it on the MLS, and forget about it&lt;/strong&gt;. However, there are plenty of real estate agents out there doing much more, so today I wanted to share some different marketing strategies in place that are low-cost and can be used with all of your listings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of the tips I discussed, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:07 - Blog your MLS descriptions on your website&lt;br /&gt;1:35 - Using Pinterest to market a listing&lt;br /&gt;1:54 - How to use Facebook to your advantage&lt;br /&gt;2:35 - Make a video of the listing and create a unique website&lt;br /&gt;2:55 - Why Instagram and Craigslist can also be useful marketing strategies&lt;br /&gt;3:30 - Using Facebook Marketplace as a marketing technique&lt;br /&gt;3:50 - Zillow advertising&lt;br /&gt;4:25 - Promote the listing to other agents that you know&lt;br /&gt;5:40 - Start promoting the listing to a targeted group of buyers&lt;br /&gt;6:50 - How and why we utilize all of these techniques for our agents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about any of the techniques we talked about today or about anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/low-cost-marketing-techniques-you-can-implement.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/low-cost-marketing-techniques-you-can-implement.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Ways to Leverage the Nextdoor App for Free</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HdrXBASoHKU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have you heard of the Nextdoor app? If not, you may be missing out on a great tool for your business.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The internet is giving consumers more ways to communicate with one another than ever. &lt;strong&gt;They can trade information, share resources, and give advice on people to hire&lt;/strong&gt;. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://nextdoor.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nextdoor &lt;/a&gt;app is a free and private social network for neighborhoods, and it allows area residents to talk and collaborate among each other online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These groups are called trusted communities—&lt;strong&gt;the people who make it up all share something in common&lt;/strong&gt;. In this case, they live in the same area. Regardless of what it is they have in common, they’re more willing to trust other members of the same community. If one person trusts you as an agent, they’ll spread the word to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To help you take advantage of this great resource, today we’ll be going over three ways you can leverage the Nextdoor app in your business for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you use these tactics, you’ll be able to boost your business through Nextdoor.%20MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/3-ways-to-leverage-the-nextdoor-app-for-free.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you use these tactics, you’ll be able to boost your business through Nextdoor.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, I’ve included timestamps of today’s topic. Feel free to navigate to the section(s) you’re most interested in viewing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:06 - Introduction to our topic: Leveraging the Nextdoor app&lt;br /&gt;0:53 - An overview of Nextdoor&lt;br /&gt;1:48 - Why I don’t recommend paying for advertising on Nextdoor&lt;br /&gt;2:42 - Tip No. 1: Make open house announcements&lt;br /&gt;6:38 - Tip No. 2: Make new listing announcements&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - Tip No. 3: Use your own community&lt;br /&gt;9:02 - Conclusion to today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use these tactics, you’ll be able to boost your business through Nextdoor—for free! If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/3-ways-to-leverage-the-nextdoor-app-for-free.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/3-ways-to-leverage-the-nextdoor-app-for-free.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Generate More Business in Just 24 Hours With These 3 Tips</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Xdkw85X2Th0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing three lead generation tips that can help you gain more business in less than 24 hours.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acquiring new leads doesn’t have to be complicated. In fact, today I’ll be sharing three simple things you can do to generate leads in the next 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:37 - An introduction to today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:58 - Tip No. 1: Text 40 people from your personal contact lists&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:26 - The script you can use for this text message to your contacts and why it works&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:24 - Tip No. 2: Text 100 people from your database&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:27 - The script to use for this message to your database and why it works&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:46 - Tip No. 3: Create a simple email inviting leads to act on their real estate goals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:56 - An example of the results you can see by utilizing these tips&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:26 - A message about the Harrelson Group’s current growth and how we can help you expand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give my team or me a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/generate-more-business-in-just-24-hours-with-these-3-tips.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/generate-more-business-in-just-24-hours-with-these-3-tips.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
