<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Myrtle Beach Real Estate Podcast with Greg Harrelson</title>
    <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Harrelson Group - your professional Myrtle Beach Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Greg Harrelson</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-08-03 16:23:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Greg Harrelson</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>gregharrelson@gmail.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Greg Harrelson</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Myrtle Beach Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Harrelson Group - your professional Myrtle Beach Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>22 Listings in His First 55 Days</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/22-listings-in-his-first-55-days.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-02 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Are you worried about making it in real estate?

Learn how Greg Harrelson is working with a new agent, Jason Wang, and they did in order for Jason to  take 22 listings in his first 55 days of being licensed.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Are you worried about making it in real estate?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Are you worried about making it in real estate?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Making Connections, Not Just Contacts</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/making-connections-not-just-contacts.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-07-12 10:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Making+Connections.mp4</guid>
        <description>

With all the technology at our disposal, we have never been more disconnected as a society. This is having a real impact on our business as real estate agents. Why are meaningful connections more important than the volume of contacts? What are some ways to deepen the connection with a contact? How can you track your connections and come up with a good metric to measure them? On this episode, we talk about the importance of forming a meaningful connection with people, and how it benefits your business.

“To get business, we have to make true and authentic connections with people. -Greg Harrelson”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Clients are calling back the people they have the strongest connection with.
  The length of time between when you capture a lead and do business with them is a lot longer now, and a real connection will get you through that process.
  Don’t focus on the length of conversations– focus on asking questions.
  Scripts can be very helpful, as they are filled with questions that lead towards genuine connections.


Want to Know Where Greg Harrelson Gets His DATA?Click here: https://www.colerealtyresource.com/landing/realestatesalessolutions/
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Making+Connections.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Making+Connections.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>To get business, we have to make true and authentic connections with people.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>To get business, we have to make true and authentic connections with people.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Tech Companies Can Impact the Future of the Buyer Agent</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-tech-companies-can-impact-the-future-of-the-buyer-agent.html</link>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-17 10:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/impact+the+future.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Technology is causing so many great changes that it can be hard to keep up with it all. What can you do to avoid being negatively affected by shifts in the industry? Is there a threat of our commissions being decreased? What changes might technology bring to buyer’s agents, and how do we adapt to an industry moving so quickly? On this episode, we talk about how agents can prepare themselves for what’s to come.  

“The experience we provide needs to not only be a “wow” experience, but a relevant “wow” experience.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Real estate agents have to learn how to survive when there’s pressure on commissions.
  Right now, it’s better to have a smaller database with high engagement and high connectivity than a large database.
  Our primary value to the market isn’t negotiation– it’s marketing and attracting the right types of buyers.


In the future, real estate agents might make less money, but this does not mean that the consumer is paying less. It means that the piece of the commission pie might get smaller because it’s being distributed amongst additional players. We’re progressing to a point where tech companies will have a bigger stake in real estate. There will constantly be new things coming in from technology companies that will make it easier for consumers, agents and tech companies to justify getting a small piece of the transaction. Agents will have to learn how to thrive when there’s pressure on commissions.

InfusionSoft for real estate. Get up and running fast with our Real Estate Package! 9 pre-built Infusionsoft campaigns, all ready to go.

Connect on Facebook. Follow Greg for more motivational content to take your real estate business to the next level
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/impact+the+future.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/impact+the+future.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The experience we provide needs to not only be a “wow” experience, but a relevant “wow” experience.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The experience we provide needs to not only be a “wow” experience, but a relevant “wow” experience.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Increasing Your Market Share in a Hot Market</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/increasing-your-market-share-in-a-hot-market.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-10 10:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Increasing+Your+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

In a hot market, skilled agents find themselves competing with less skilled agents for clients who may not be able to see the difference right away. How do you prove yourself when the consumer isn’t really looking for skill? Why is a down market actually a lot easier to grow in? How do you go about growing your market share when so many people want a piece of the pie? On this episode, we talk about what it takes to grow your business when the market is up.

“Focus on the systems you have in place and make small tweaks. Then let the compound effect be the reason why you gain market share.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  In a down market the consumer is hiring for skills; But in a hot market they’re just hiring warm bodies.
  There are still plenty of transactions in a down market– there are just fewer agents going after them.
  Don’t reinvent the wheel or focus on shiny objects. Double down on what’s working already.


In a hot market, you get more people with low skill sets flocking to the real estate industry because they think they can make some quick money. In a down market these people leave the business and the skilled agents are in much higher demand. In a hot market, we have more money to buy more shiny objects and open up more circles that we never complete. Those things become distractions that stunt growth. In a down market there are less distractions, and the agents with skill and experience rise to the top, especially when they focus on what works.

Learn more about Infusionsoft for real estate: http://www.realestatesalessolutions.com/
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Increasing+Your+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Increasing+Your+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this episode, we talk about what it takes to grow your business when the market is up.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this episode, we talk about what it takes to grow your business when the market is up.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Self-Leadership</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/self-leadership.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-22 09:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Self-leadership.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’re all leaders because we lead ourselves. Why do you have to be a good self-leader before you’re qualified to lead others effectively? What makes someone a great leader? On this mini-episode, we talk about how to be a better leader, and the secret so few people know about leadership.

“You must be the example for other people to follow.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  You have to be an effective self-leader before you lead others because it gives you credibility.
  If you’re having trouble leading others, you have problems with self-leadership.
  You must be the example for other people to follow.  


A lot of people have a hard time attracting loyal followers because they weren’t followers themselves in the first place. They don’t lead themselves, and that makes it impossible for them to lead others. The truth about leadership is you become better by becoming a great learner, and a great player who follows a great coach. It all starts with you, so ask yourself if you’re a great follower of the things that you say and if you have integrity with the things you tell people do.

Learn more about Infusionsoft for real estate: http://www.realestatesalessolutions.com/
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Self-leadership.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Self-leadership.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this mini-episode, we talk about how to be a better leader, and the secret so few people know about leadership.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this mini-episode, we talk about how to be a better leader, and the secret so few people know about leadership.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Anticipating the Obstacle and Creating the Solution</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/anticipating-the-obstacle-and-creating-the-solution.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-01 09:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Anticipating+the+Obstacles.mp4</guid>
        <description>

This is the time of the year where we evaluate the market for potential risks, and a huge one right now is the risk for low inventory. Why is it so important to plan ahead for these events? How do you fortify yourself from the eventual reduction in inventory? On this episode, we talk about the importance of being ready for potential market risks.

“When I’m already solving a problem that doesn’t yet exist, the problem never appears.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  There’s a lot of quick, easy money on the buyer’s side right now, so people don’t think they need listings.
  If the market continues to rise, sellers are going to slow the pace of houses on the market because they are playing the market for appreciation.
  The two most effective ways to generate leads in a low-inventory environment are expireds and FSBOs.


The goal in business is to always start working a plan as if an upcoming obstacle is there now. You have to set up the systems right now to combat the risks when they do appear. Just because there’s a lot of buying happening right now, don’t fall into the trap of not building up your listings. If inventory to sell runs out, you’re in a better position if you’ve been cultivating listings. Right now, you have a good story to tell sellers in prospecting which is that prices are increasing and inventory is low, so their house could be worth more. That’s a winning script.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Anticipating+the+Obstacles.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Anticipating+the+Obstacles.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>we talk about the importance of being ready for potential market risks.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>we talk about the importance of being ready for potential market risks.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Developing Talent</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/developing-talent.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-01-11 10:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Developing+Talent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Developing talent is an important part of going from agent to entrepreneur. How do you connect with your talent on a level that actually resonates with them and their needs? What are the three things we track to make sure what we’re doing is actually working? How do you check in and stay in contact? On this mini-episode, we talk about developing talent, helping people grow and building top producers from scratch.

“Tracking our numbers is going to tell us how we’re doing with our lead generation activities and the conversations we’re having.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  If you can leverage a person’s strengths, you can get to revenue more easily.
  You’ll be able to leverage their strengths faster than you can strengthen their weaknesses.  
  Every transaction is going to come from a conversation.


Most people’s first instinct when it comes to developing talent is to try and get people emotionally invested and fired up by the possibilities they see for that person. What you should actually do first is connect with them on what’s important to them. Honor them by showing that you actually want to know them. When you get into their world you will understand them better. When you do that, their mindset changes, they gain confidence and they become more coachable. This will get you to more income, faster.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Developing+Talent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Developing+Talent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this mini-episode, we talk about developing talent, helping people grow and building top producers from scratch.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this mini-episode, we talk about developing talent, helping people grow and building top producers from scratch.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Eliminate Resistance to Prospecting & Lead Generation</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-to-eliminate-resistance-to-prospecting-lead-generation.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2017-11-09 10:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Eliminate+Resistance.mp4</guid>
        <description>

People are looking for a method of lead generation and prospecting that feels comfortable to them. However, this comfort is dictated by bias—not reality. How do you get inspired to make a breakthrough in your resistance to prospecting? Why do people struggle to say they are salespeople? How do you use contribution to get over the monetary motivation? On this episode, we discuss the real reason people resist prospecting and how to overcome it.

“I got over a resistance to prospecting when I changed my perspective.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Contribution goals can be more effective than monetary goals.
  People don’t want to say they are a great salesperson because they associate sales with something bad.
  Change your goal from “how much money you want to make” to how many families you want to help and that will make the job about contribution.


At the start of the show, we talked about why people are always looking for a lead generation method that feels comfortable. Next, we talked about the power of shifting your mindset if you want to get better at lead generation. We also talked about why people don’t want to be associated with being good at sales.

We also discussed:


  How to change your goals from money to contribution
  How to change your perspectives of prospecting activities


It is impossible to successfully overcome hesitation towards prospecting and lead generation without a mindset shift. For most people, the resistance comes from wanting to be comfortable and not wanting to face the limiting beliefs they have about selling. When you change your goals from “make money” to “make a contribution”, you will overcome the fear of being good at selling. When you change your perception of that activity, your comfort level will greatly increase.

Resources

InfusionSoft for real estate. Get up and running fast with our Real Estate Package! 9 pre-built Infusionsoft campaigns, all ready to go.

Connect on Facebook. Follow Greg for more motivational content to take your real estate business to the next level
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Eliminate+Resistance.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Eliminate+Resistance.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this episode, we discuss the real reason people resist prospecting and how to overcome it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this episode, we discuss the real reason people resist prospecting and how to overcome it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Distractions, Momentum & Opportunity: How To Clean Up in a Distracted Market</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/distractions-momentum-opportunity-how-to-clean-up-in-a-distracted-market.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2017-10-12 11:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Distractions.mp4</guid>
        <description>

With everything happening in the world right now, the consumer is more distracted than ever. How can this cause a shift in momentum in the market? How do you offset the potential losses? How do you bring attention back to what’s important and have the right conversations with your clients? On this episode, we discuss how to maintain momentum, even when people are focused on everything that’s happening in the world.

“When the distraction of the consumer increases, the answer for the agent is to actually decrease distraction and increase their number of contacts.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  There are distractions you can control and distractions you cannot control.
  Right now, the market is so good that it’s even rewarding people who aren’t skilled or efficient.
  Media companies monetize distraction.
  Don’t communicate about the transaction, communicate the motivation.


At the start of the show, we discussed the various things that are distracting the consumer, and what it has to do with the news. Next, we discussed what would go wrong if the both the consumer and the agent are distracted. We also talked about the power of showing people that you really care, and that you want what is best for them. Towards the end of the show, we talked about how people attract business by treating people like they are already your clients.

We also discussed:


  How to get better at asking good questions and listening
  How to increase your activity when the market slows down
  How distraction creates inactivity


Distractions give people a sense of uncertainty. When people feel uncertain, they tend not to make a lot of decisions. If the consumer’s distraction and inaction is coupled with the agent’s inactivity, this can have a huge impact on the market. As an agent, it is your job to limit distractions by having better conversations. In the face of a distractions, keep your client focused on their motivation. Remember: people’s motivation isn’t “to sell a house”, but to acquire the benefits that come along as a result of the sale. If you want to succeed in this distraction-laden market, decrease distraction in your interactions and increase your number of contacts.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Distractions.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Distractions.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this episode, we discuss how to maintain momentum, even when people are focused on everything that’s happening in the world.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this episode, we discuss how to maintain momentum, even when people are focused on everything that’s happening in the world.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Art of Relentless Prospecting</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-art-of-relentless-prospecting.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2017-07-13 11:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Relentless+Prospecting.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Many real estate agents prospect for appointments but end up fearing the appointment itself. Why is that? How can we overcome our fear of rejection and make it work for us? Can building a boring day-to-day life really make us successful? In this episode, we reframe rejection and boredom as the key to success.

“If you will go ahead and master the listing presentation first, then you’re excited to make the call”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Agents gravitate toward buyers to avoid rejection and limit their personal growth and their business all at the same time.
  Even when you lose a listing, sellers aren’t rejecting you, they are rejecting your WORDS - something you said during the listing consultation.
  Boredom is about YOU. Change your focus to the people you are serving and you won’t feel boredom.


Resources

InfusionSoft for real estate. Get up and running fast with our Real Estate Package! 9 pre-built Infusionsoft campaigns, all ready to go.

Connect on Facebook. Follow Greg for more motivational content to take your real estate business to the next level

First we talked about building a career out of prospecting and the newfound prospecting generation with real estate agents. We also discussed the benefits of prospecting and its sticking points. Next, we talked about why some people subconsciously avoid prospecting and getting a listing appointment. We agreed that by mastering the listing presentation, then you’ll be less hesitant to get on the phone and get that appointment. We also mentioned how empathy and creating a prospecting ritual can not only benefit the client but also the agent themselves. Finally, we mentioned how appreciation for that style of work grows over time as you get more and more committed to your prospecting ritual.

On this episode we also discussed:


  How failure to follow up can lead to losses
  Overcoming the fear of rejection
  The importance of consistency
  Sustainable boredom and its benefits
  Minimizing distractions through rituals
  and much more


It’s critical to be consistent and persistent at the same time. Rejection is something we will all have to face at some point - so it’s important to reconsider the way we think about being rejected and focus on how to avoid that rejection for the next listing.

And when we talk about consistency, most of the time, boredom has to be a part of the conversation as well. Being boring is now a sustainable choice and a sensible solution for a business. It’s all about installing some variety in your boring day-to-day activities. Mastering that balance and shifting your perspective on rejection and boredom can be a solid way to get more listings and build a successful real estate business.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Relentless+Prospecting.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Relentless+Prospecting.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>In this episode, we reframe rejection and boredom as the key to success.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>In this episode, we reframe rejection and boredom as the key to success.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Greg Harrelson</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Greg Harrelson</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Harrelson Group - your professional Myrtle Beach Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
