<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Myrtle Beach Real Estate Podcast with Greg Harrelson</title>
    <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Harrelson Group - your professional Myrtle Beach Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Greg Harrelson</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-08-19 11:00:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Greg Harrelson</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>gregharrelson@gmail.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Greg Harrelson</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Myrtle Beach Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Harrelson Group - your professional Myrtle Beach Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Objection or Question? Knowing the Difference</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/objection-or-question-knowing-the-difference.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-07-18 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/Objection+or+Question_+Knowing+the+Difference.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Sometimes clients ask their agents questions, but the agents hear them as objections. What&rsquo;s the difference?

 

If a client or a prospect asks a real estate agent a question, the agent needs to be very careful about interpreting it as an objection. Sometimes it’s a knee-jerk reaction to treat someone’s questions that way, but when you respond to a question as though it were an objection, all you’ve done is create the objection.

Here’s an example to help illustrate what I mean:

Suppose that a prospect was to ask you, “Will you cut your commission fee?” That’s a question, but many agents would hear that as an objection and start listing all the reasons why they can’t or shouldn’t cut the commission.

In reality, it really was just a question. Instead of framing it as an objection, try giving some response to the effect of, “You know, I’m sorry, but I can’t do that. Do you have any other questions?” That way, you can give them an honest answer and move on to their other queries. If the question comes up again, then you can start treating it like an objection.

Here’s some roleplay to expound upon my example:

Client - “Will you cut your commission fee?”

Agent -  “You know, I’m sorry, but I can’t do that. Do you have any other questions?”

Client - “Well, another agent told me that they would, and that’s one of the things we’re considering when we compare different agents.”

“I believe that half the time when people ask us these questions, they’re not doing so to raise an objection.”

With that last response, you now know that it’s an objection, and you may need to dig a little deeper in order to handle the objection and win over the business.

From my experience, I believe that half the time when people ask us these questions, they’re not doing so to raise an objection. By following the methods that I’ve shared today, you won’t have as many objections to handle.

If you have any questions about this or other topics, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to hear from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/Objection+or+Question_+Knowing+the+Difference.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/Objection+or+Question_+Knowing+the+Difference.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Sometimes clients ask their agents questions, but the agents hear them as objections. What’s the difference?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Sometimes clients ask their agents questions, but the agents hear them as objections. What’s the difference?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Coaching & How to Find the Right Coach for You</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-importance-of-coaching-how-to-find-the-right-coach-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-30 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Importance+of+Coaching+%26+How+to+Find+the+Right+Coach+for+You.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I believe that every real estate agent should have a coach&mdash;here&rsquo;s why.

 

If you’re looking to build and sustain a profitable business, then you need to hire a coach. I believe all real estate agents (and all professionals in any industry) should hire a coach.

Why? No matter how well you’re doing, you can still do more with less effort, and this is where a coach can help you. You can be making money, but a coach can make you more profitable. Additionally, people only seem to want to hire a coach when they’re not doing so well, but if you wait until business falters to hire a coach, you have to deal with the challenge of actually paying that coach.

Now, with that in mind, here are three tips that will help you hire the right coach.

First, choose a coach who’s walked the walk. There are a lot of coaches out there who’re willing to take your money but haven’t actually done the level of business you might already be doing. I know coaches who’ve sold 30 or 40 properties a year with a team of eight people and now they want to educate others on how to build a team. Here’s the thing, though: An eight-man team isn’t profitable only selling 30 to 40 properties a year.

Learn from someone who’s experienced and has actually produced at a high level instead of just read a book—coaching from experience is a lot better than coaching from a book. Also, make sure they’ve produced year after year and they’re not a one-hit wonder. In other words, a coach can average 20 deals a year and then all of a sudden reach 70 deals one year, but only because they bought a bunch of Zillow leads. That’s not the kind of coaching you want to look for.

Second, choose a coach who’s present all the time. Think about professional sports teams who practice every day in between their actual games. Their coaches are with them at every practice and on the sidelines during the games. They’re not just watching them on TV. Similarly, you want a coach who’s present all the time instead of someone who’s with you one hour per week and then disappears.

“No matter how well you’re doing, you can still do more with less effort, and this is where a coach can help you.”

Third, pick somebody who’s willing to tell you what you don’t want to hear when you don’t want to hear it. A lot of coaches out there are great cheerleaders, but real growth comes from coaches who hold you accountable and can tell you about things you can do better. Don’t hire a cheerleader. Instead, hire someone who wants to help you develop and wants you to be their next top producer.

I know it’s hard to find coaching that matches these exact criteria, but when you do, that’s when you’ll find other top producers. These agents surround themselves with a coaching environment that’s constant, and if you want to take your business to the next level, you need to align yourself with coaching companies that provide this.

The reality is, you can’t pay for this type of coaching. Just a weekly 30-minute session alone would cost you $1,000. If you find the right company and align yourself with them, though, you’ll receive their coaching as one of their value adds.

I have expert advisors in Charleston and Century 21 Vanguard in Columbia, and we have these kinds of coaching programs in place. We coach agents every day on how to grow their business in a profitable manner, so if you’d like to do the same for your business, don’t hesitate to call or email me so we can get started.

If you have any other real estate questions, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Importance+of+Coaching+%26+How+to+Find+the+Right+Coach+for+You.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Importance+of+Coaching+%26+How+to+Find+the+Right+Coach+for+You.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I believe that every real estate agent should have a coach—here’s why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I believe that every real estate agent should have a coach—here’s why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Drive Eyes to Your Listings in 3 Simple Steps</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/drive-eyes-to-your-listings-in-3-simple-steps.html</link>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-12 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Drive+Eyes+to+Your+Listings+in+3+Simple+Steps.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I&rsquo;ve got a fun, quick challenge for you to complete this Friday. Here&rsquo;s what you need to do.

 

I recently had an idea that I decided to turn into a challenge. Usually when I challenge you, it’s to take an action that I know is going to bring a big benefit back to you and your business. It’s also usually something that is simple and free. This challenge is no exception.

Here’s what I created: The Friday Facebook Challenge. It’s very simple and will only take about five minutes. I challenge every one of you to follow this system today:

1. Take one of your listings or a company listing and post it on your personal Facebook page today. Posting to your personal page will ensure that the people we want to attract (your sphere) see the post.

2. Include “Featured listing by (your name) at (company name)” with a link under that line to the listing. The branding here is invaluable and will direct traffic to the listing.

3. Keep up with the post throughout the day to see if it has been liked, commented on, or shared. If somebody shares the post with someone specific, you can bet they are looking for a home that fits the criteria. The person who shared it with them tips us off to the lead, who you can then reach out to. We have used this strategy and gotten leads, set appointments, and written contracts.

“If someone shares the post on Facebook, keep a close eye on the person who they share it with.”

There you go. Your Friday Facebook Challenge is quick, simple, free, and effective. It can put you in a great position to get a new lead that you can start working tomorrow. If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Drive+Eyes+to+Your+Listings+in+3+Simple+Steps.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Drive+Eyes+to+Your+Listings+in+3+Simple+Steps.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’ve got a fun, quick challenge for you to complete this Friday. Here’s what you need to do.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’ve got a fun, quick challenge for you to complete this Friday. Here’s what you need to do.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Are the Biggest Challenges Facing Agents in Today’s Market?</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/what-are-the-biggest-challenges-facing-agents-in-todays-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-05-29 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+What+Are+the+Biggest+Challenges+Facing+Agents+in+Todays+Market_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I&rsquo;ve been seeing agents struggle more and more with certain aspects of the real estate business. These are the three problems I&rsquo;ve noticed the most.

 

I’m always keeping an eye on the market, so today I want to talk about three of the challenges I see real estate agents facing right now when trying to build their business or break through to the next level:

1. Being too late to the lead. A lot of agents are struggling with the “speed to lead” concept. By the time many agents reach out to a lead, the lead has already spoken to another agent. That’s not a new concept. You already know the challenges that can happen when you don’t have that speed. Could you be throttling your leads based on your availability? If you know you’re going to be out all afternoon, why would you generate leads during that time when you’re not going to be able to reach out quickly? I’m not a proponent of turning your lead flow off, but you do have to ask yourself why would you have them if you can’t use them.

2. Managing consumers’ nurture demands. The demands of agents have changed with our consumers. The challenge is that now we’re capturing the lead so much earlier in the process than we used to. It requires a much more longer-term nurture. Instead of being ready to buy in 30 days, they might not be ready for another 18 months. Those leads require two different nurture programs, but not all agents have caught up to that fact yet. When you’re building a nurture campaign these days, you need to make sure they combine multiple avenues (text, call, email, Facebook messages, etc.). You’ll need multiple channels in order to win the attention of leads in today’s real estate world.

“Anything can work if you give it 100%.”

3. Focusing on the one thing that works. Just about everything works if you just give it 100% of your effort. Whether you choose to go the open house route, the direct mail route, or the FSBO route, all of these strategies can work, but they won’t all work at the same time. Pick one or two areas and put 100% of your effort in for 90 days at the minimum and you’ll generate tremendous momentum.

These are the three biggest struggles I’m seeing with agents in today’s market. If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I would love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+What+Are+the+Biggest+Challenges+Facing+Agents+in+Todays+Market_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+What+Are+the+Biggest+Challenges+Facing+Agents+in+Todays+Market_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>These are the three problems I’ve noticed the most.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>These are the three problems I’ve noticed the most.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Did We Get 816 Listings in Q1 2019?</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-did-we-get-816-listings-in-q1-2019.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-05-15 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+How+Did+We+Get+816+Listings+in+Q1+2019_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Year to date, the Harrelson Group has gotten over 816 listings. How did we do it? Find out right here.

 

In just the first quarter of 2019, we had 816 listings, but by the time you read this, the Harrelson Group will probably have well over 900 listings under our belt. But how do we do that?

Well first, I may own our brokerage, but I run it like a team. Each of our team members is independently building their own business—I just happen to be the coach providing the systems, leads, training, and resources needed to build a business.

At the end of 2018, we began to set goals and make commitments. Our goal was to increase the number of listings taken and improve our inventory levels. So many people were upset about how hard it was to find listings in our low-inventory market.

Next, we committed to collaboration. As a group, we brainstormed tactics for increasing the number of listings we would take and created hundreds of ideas on how we could obtain new listings. Each individual agent then decided which of those ideas they wanted to focus on; some focused on just one tactic, and others focused on executing five or 10 different ideas.

At our office, we have a saying: “Your goal is my goal.” We’re constantly setting goals and working together to help our team members actually achieve those goals, and time has shown that when we help out fellow agents do better in their business, we become better ourselves.

“Making goals, collaborating, holding each other accountable, and executing strategies are key if you want to grow your listing inventory.”

In our team-oriented environment, we also hold each other accountable. When someone creates a big goal to meet, there will always be times when they don’t feel like showing up or taking action on the commitments they made. But on our team, when one agent sees another slipping up, they’ll reach out and prod them on and ask how they can help get them back on track. A team environment pushes everybody to the top.

Lastly, we took action to actually execute our goals. We didn’t just call 5,000 homeowners and get 816 listings—there are so many ways to get listings. Our success is due to our focus on the approach, not on our methods of getting the listings themselves.

Making goals, collaborating, holding each other accountable, and executing strategies are key if you want to grow your listing inventory. The challenge that most people have is being all by themselves. On a team, we put our heads together to help each other figure it out.

Follow this model of approach and just see what will happen to your business over the next three or four months. If you have any questions, feel free to give me a call or send an email. I’d love to talk with you about how to create this type of environment in your own brokerage.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+How+Did+We+Get+816+Listings+in+Q1+2019_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+How+Did+We+Get+816+Listings+in+Q1+2019_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Year to date, the Harrelson Group has gotten over 816 listings. How did we do it? Find out right here.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Year to date, the Harrelson Group has gotten over 816 listings. How did we do it? Find out right here.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>You Shouldn’t Care if the Market Shifts—Here’s Why</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/you-shouldnt-care-if-the-market-shiftsheres-why.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-05-01 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/You+Shouldnt+Care+if+the+Market+ShiftsHeres+Why.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you set your business up correctly, you needn&rsquo;t be worried about a market shift. Here are three tips to help you do just that.

 

As a professional agent, should you care if our market shifts?

If you set your business up correctly, the answer is no. If anything, a market shift can help you because it will lead to more part-time agents switching careers and leaving a bigger piece of the pie behind.

We don’t want anybody to suffer because of a downturn, but for some, this is inevitable. If you want to keep your business stable in the face of a market shift, there are three tips you need to follow that will help you focus on helping your clients instead of just surviving.

For your convenience, I’ve timestamped each of these tips and how you can apply them so you can skip ahead in the video above at your leisure:


  2:00 - Go lean
  4:03 - Collaborate
  5:38 - Be active, not passive


“Fewer expenses + more ideas + more leads = more business no matter what the market does.”

No matter what’s going on in your local market, you need to follow these three tips. Another way to think of them is by breaking them down into this simple formula: fewer expenses + more ideas + more leads = more business no matter what the market does.

We care very much about putting our clients in the best financial position possible during a market shift, but we shouldn’t have to stress out over our business.

If you’d like to talk more about how to thrive instead of merely survive during a market shift, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/You+Shouldnt+Care+if+the+Market+ShiftsHeres+Why.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/You+Shouldnt+Care+if+the+Market+ShiftsHeres+Why.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>If you set your business up correctly, you needn’t be worried about a market shift. Here are three tips to help you do just that.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>If you set your business up correctly, you needn’t be worried about a market shift. Here are three tips to help you do just that.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The 3 Mindsets Choices That Can Boost Your Real Estate Career</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-3-mindsets-choices-that-can-boost-your-real-estate-career.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-14 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+The+3+Mindsets+Choices+That+Can+Boost+Your+Real+Estate+Career.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Your attitude, approach, and expectations play a key role in your business. Here&rsquo;s what you should do to keep them positive.

 

There are three things you can change in your mindset that will help you get more out of your real estate business.

There are many distractions and frustrations that come at us throughout each day. How we manage these trials is up to our attitude, approach, and expectations.

Take a look at your attitude. Do you see the glass as half empty or half full? Are things problems or opportunities? Your attitude affects how you view situations, and if you see things as pains and problems, you’re much less likely to want to deal with them. If you take things as challenges that you can solve, you’ll do much better in your business.

Let’s say you get a lowball offer—it can be discouraging and may put you in a negative mindset. If you think, “This is never going to work out,” how is that going to affect your approach? Think of it this way: You got an offer, which means you’re better off than when you had none. Then, it’s time to figure out how you can negotiate it into something better.

“Ultimately, your attitude, approach, and expectations will influence your final results.”

If you’re feeling discouraged and upset, your approach will reflect that. That approach further harms your expectations. If you feel like everything is going to fail, and you act like everything is going to fail, then what are you going to expect of the end result? If you don’t expect a positive outcome, it’ll be hard for your client to expect one.

Your client will mirror your actions. If you’re positive, they’ll stay positive as well, but if you’re negative, they’ll also follow suit. With a negative outlook, deals that could be salvaged are instead being thrown away. Ultimately, your attitude, approach, and expectations will influence your final results. These results are generated from your clients’ feelings, so it’s up to you whether you want the outcome to be good or bad.

If you want good results, have a great attitude when it’s difficult. Things will rarely be perfect, but if you can stay positive through the pain, you will win in the end.

If you have any questions or would like to talk about building your business, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+The+3+Mindsets+Choices+That+Can+Boost+Your+Real+Estate+Career.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+The+3+Mindsets+Choices+That+Can+Boost+Your+Real+Estate+Career.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Your attitude, approach, and expectations play a key role in your business. Here’s what you should do to keep them positive.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Your attitude, approach, and expectations play a key role in your business. Here’s what you should do to keep them positive.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Low-Cost Marketing Techniques You Can Implement</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/low-cost-marketing-techniques-you-can-implement.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-13 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Low-Cost+Marketing+Techniques+You+Can+Implement.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Marketing is one of the most important parts of selling a home. Here are some inexpensive, effective techniques that we use for our listings.

 

I’m sure you’ve been in a situation where you’ve talked to a seller client after a few weeks and they want to know what you’ve done to market their home.

A lot of times, sellers think that all an agent does is take a listing, set it on the MLS, and forget about it. However, there are plenty of real estate agents out there doing much more, so today I wanted to share some different marketing strategies in place that are low-cost and can be used with all of your listings.

Here’s an outline of the tips I discussed, with timestamps so that you can skip ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most:

1:07 - Blog your MLS descriptions on your website1:35 - Using Pinterest to market a listing1:54 - How to use Facebook to your advantage2:35 - Make a video of the listing and create a unique website2:55 - Why Instagram and Craigslist can also be useful marketing strategies3:30 - Using Facebook Marketplace as a marketing technique3:50 - Zillow advertising4:25 - Promote the listing to other agents that you know5:40 - Start promoting the listing to a targeted group of buyers6:50 - How and why we utilize all of these techniques for our agents

If you have any questions about any of the techniques we talked about today or about anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Low-Cost+Marketing+Techniques+You+Can+Implement.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Low-Cost+Marketing+Techniques+You+Can+Implement.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are some inexpensive, effective techniques that we use for our listings.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are some inexpensive, effective techniques that we use for our listings.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Ways to Leverage the Nextdoor App for Free</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/3-ways-to-leverage-the-nextdoor-app-for-free.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-03 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+3+Ways+to+Leverage+the+Nextdoor+App+for+Free.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Have you heard of the Nextdoor app? If not, you may be missing out on a great tool for your business.

 

The internet is giving consumers more ways to communicate with one another than ever. They can trade information, share resources, and give advice on people to hire. The Nextdoor app is a free and private social network for neighborhoods, and it allows area residents to talk and collaborate among each other online.

These groups are called trusted communities—the people who make it up all share something in common. In this case, they live in the same area. Regardless of what it is they have in common, they’re more willing to trust other members of the same community. If one person trusts you as an agent, they’ll spread the word to others.

To help you take advantage of this great resource, today we’ll be going over three ways you can leverage the Nextdoor app in your business for free.

“If you use these tactics, you’ll be able to boost your business through Nextdoor.”

For your convenience, I’ve included timestamps of today’s topic. Feel free to navigate to the section(s) you’re most interested in viewing:

0:06 - Introduction to our topic: Leveraging the Nextdoor app0:53 - An overview of Nextdoor1:48 - Why I don’t recommend paying for advertising on Nextdoor2:42 - Tip No. 1: Make open house announcements6:38 - Tip No. 2: Make new listing announcements7:30 - Tip No. 3: Use your own community9:02 - Conclusion to today’s topic

If you use these tactics, you’ll be able to boost your business through Nextdoor—for free! If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+3+Ways+to+Leverage+the+Nextdoor+App+for+Free.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+3+Ways+to+Leverage+the+Nextdoor+App+for+Free.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Have you heard of the Nextdoor app?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Have you heard of the Nextdoor app?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Generate More Business in Just 24 Hours With These 3 Tips</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/generate-more-business-in-just-24-hours-with-these-3-tips.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-27 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Generate+More+Business+in+Just+24+Hours+With+These+3+Tips.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I&rsquo;ll be sharing three lead generation tips that can help you gain more business in less than 24 hours.

 

Acquiring new leads doesn’t have to be complicated. In fact, today I’ll be sharing three simple things you can do to generate leads in the next 24 hours.

Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:

0:37 - An introduction to today’s topic

0:58 - Tip No. 1: Text 40 people from your personal contact lists

1:26 - The script you can use for this text message to your contacts and why it works

3:24 - Tip No. 2: Text 100 people from your database

3:27 - The script to use for this message to your database and why it works

4:46 - Tip No. 3: Create a simple email inviting leads to act on their real estate goals

5:56 - An example of the results you can see by utilizing these tips

6:26 - A message about the Harrelson Group’s current growth and how we can help you expand

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give my team or me a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Generate+More+Business+in+Just+24+Hours+With+These+3+Tips.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Generate+More+Business+in+Just+24+Hours+With+These+3+Tips.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’ll be sharing three lead generation tips that can help you gain more business in less than 24 hours.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’ll be sharing three lead generation tips that can help you gain more business in less than 24 hours.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Open Your Eyes to the Value You Deserve</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/open-your-eyes-to-the-value-you-deserve.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-10 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Open+Your+Eyes+to+the+Value+You+Deserve.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Is your broker providing you the resources you need to grow your business? If not, perhaps it&rsquo;s time to talk to them about it.

 

Are you tired of brokers asking you what you’re going to do to grow your business, or bring more listings into the company, or write more contracts?

Oftentimes, brokers ask these types of questions not to help you, but to know how you can help them earn their income. In other words, a broker’s income is really nothing more than a commission they earn for the services they provide to you, while your income is the commission you earn from the services you provide to buyers and sellers.

What is your broker doing to earn the money you’re making for them, though? That’s an interesting conversation, and I’m by no means trying to start a feud between you and the company you work for, but I do think that both parties have a responsibility to provide the resources and strategies necessary for each other to grow.

Now that the new year has arrived, perhaps it’s time for you to ask yourself whether you’re getting the services and resources you need from the company you’re with. There are three common complaints I hear from agents in search of a better business model:

1. There are no leads. Either that or the leads they’re provided are very low quality and given mostly in order to appease them.

2. There’s no coaching or training. A lot of top-level professionals in all industries have a coach. Coaching can provide additional strategies you may not have thought of, the resources needed to execute those strategies, accountability, and answers to problems that are keeping your business from growing. Some companies insist that their agents hire their own coaches, but that just means they’ll have to pay another person a portion of their commission for their services, whereas I believe that should be the company’s responsibility.

3. There is too much paperwork. Again, I believe that processing listing paperwork is the company’s responsibility. I also believe that they should handle some of the marketing for those listings.

If you don’t think you’re getting the value you need from your company, should you just quit? No—I’m not saying that at all. All I’m trying to do is open your eyes to the value you deserve, and sometimes getting that value is as simple as having a conversation with your broker about what you need from them. Give them a chance to provide you with the services and resources you need. If they can’t provide these things, it’s up to you whether you want to make a move or not.

“Your company should provide you with the CRMs, strategies, and other data you need to generate listings and buyer opportunities.”

With technology so readily available to us, I believe your company should provide you with the CRMs, strategies, and other data you need to generate listings and buyer opportunities. Companies should also provide nurture programs that will allow you to convert data into commission checks.

In addition to teaching you how to generate leads, companies should also provide leads themselves. Most agents will never make a good living if they rely specifically on either self-generated leads or company-generated leads, but if you combine these two things, you’ll find yourself at the top of your business.

Again, I’m not trying to cause any problems between you and your company, but the next time you’re thinking about what you’re doing for them, ask yourself what they’re doing for you as well. If you need additional resources, talk to them and see if you can work something out. If you can’t, you might want to explore your other options.

I coach agents in the Myrtle Beach, Charleston, and Columbia areas, so if you’re in any of these marketplaces, don’t hesitate to call or email me. I’d love to sit down with you and see if I can help you advance your career.

If you have any other questions for me or there’s anything else I can help you with, feel free to reach out to me as well. I look forward to talking to you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Open+Your+Eyes+to+the+Value+You+Deserve.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Open+Your+Eyes+to+the+Value+You+Deserve.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Is your broker providing you the resources you need to grow your business? If not, perhaps it’s time to talk to them about it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Is your broker providing you the resources you need to grow your business? If not, perhaps it’s time to talk to them about it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Stay Ahead of Your Goals in the New Year</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-to-stay-ahead-of-your-goals-in-the-new-year.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-26 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+How+to+Stay+Ahead+of+Your+Goals+in+the+New+Year.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We&rsquo;d love to help you reach your 2019 goals. Here are a few tips that we recommend.

Have you ever wondered what it would take for you to start your new year ahead of your goals? Today I have three things you can do to generate momentum quickly and get ahead of your goals to make 2019 your best year yet:

1. Call your centers of influence. Everybody says this, but I want to add a twist to it. Your intention for calling these people at the beginning of the year is to identify who may be thinking about completing a real estate transaction sometime in the next calendar year. Ask them what their real estate goals are for this year to get a better idea of where their head is. If you don’t ask that question, it’s going to be hard for you to pull out the information yourself. You will find business this way, even on the first day you make 10+ phone calls.

2. Communicate with your database. Your database is a bit different than your center of influence. It is a larger group, and it’s important to leverage and monetize this group. Calling everyone in your database will result in you reaching out to a good amount of people that you may never have met in person or only met once. By consistently reaching out to these people throughout the year, you can bring them valuable content and make sure you’re a household name to them. Once you call these people, ask them the same question that you asked your center of influence, and also ask what their goals are for 2019. This method is free, effective, and will help you generate momentum fast.

“If you continue to do the same things, you’ll get the same results.”

3. Get out of your box. If you continue to do the same things, you’ll continue to get the same results. If you want to generate momentum fast and get ahead of your goals, I suggest that you get out of your box. One type of box is your lead generation strategy. If you’re only working with buyers, get out of that box and call those past buyers you have to see if any of them are interested in listing. If your box is cold-calling, get out of that box by calling FSBOs and expireds.

In other words, add another lead generation pillar to your business so you can find additional lead sources and give yourself a better chance of doing more business. Maybe getting out of your box has to do with your environment. If you feel like you’re not growing and your career has become stagnant, stop making excuses and change that environment. Find a group that will mentor, guide, and develop you in order to build your business. I’m not saying you have to change companies, but if you’re not getting what you need to grow your business, it’s time to make a change by using one of these tips above.

If you have any questions for me in the meantime about your 2019 goals or about real estate business in general, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+How+to+Stay+Ahead+of+Your+Goals+in+the+New+Year.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+How+to+Stay+Ahead+of+Your+Goals+in+the+New+Year.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’d love to help you reach your 2019 goals. Here are a few tips that we recommend.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’d love to help you reach your 2019 goals. Here are a few tips that we recommend.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Boom or Bust in 2019? Be Ready for Either With These 5 Steps</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/boom-or-bust-in-2019-be-ready-for-either-with-these-5-steps.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-06 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Boom+or+Bust+in+2019%253F+Be+Ready+for+Either+With+These+5+Steps.mp4</guid>
        <description>

What kind of growth or turbulence can we expect from the market in 2019? It may not matter to you if you apply these five steps to your own business.

 

The new year is right around the corner, and a pressing question looms over the horizon for our market—will 2019 be a boom or bust? The market is buzzing with dialogue concerning this question. While we’ve seen continued growth for agents across the board and a healthy market driving these good numbers over the last few years, it’s impossible to ignore what’s in front of us—is the market going up or down?

The prevailing sentiment among the agents I speak to is that there exists an uptick in inventory paired with an increase in days on market for that inventory, at this time. It’s important to pay attention to the increases in these areas because that signifies a potential softening of the market.

Not only that, but agents are also reporting that the flood of multiple offers they were experiencing not that long ago has dried up somewhat.

I should note that this isn’t to conclusively say that the market is headed in a downward direction—but the signs are present. Keep in mind that all the chatter we’re hearing around the issue doesn’t necessarily equate to a market slowdown.

Slowdown or no slowdown, a key question for you to consider is: Will you be prepared if the market does turn down?

“It’s important to pay attention to the increases in these areas because that signifies a potential softening of the market.”

Though market forces are out of your hands, how you respond to them makes all the difference to your success. Being diligent and adjusting when a market shift is afoot can minimize, or completely preempt, the ill effects that shift has on your business—and here are five ways in which you can accomplish this:

1. Increase lead generation without spending more money. In the event of a market shift, the idea isn’t to necessarily discontinue buying leads altogether. Instead, decrease lead flow in high-cost areas so that, in turn, you’ll have those extra dollars to increase lead flow in no- or low-cost areas and possibly grow.

2. Start communicating with your database. It’s not just about communicating with your clients—it’s about doing so with intention. Build foundational rapport with clients now so that if a market shift hits, you’ll be the trusted source they call on.

3. Surround yourself with agents focused on growing their business. Stay away from the worrywarts or those that get “paralysis through analysis.” Surround yourself with those that are motivated and persist through changing market trends.

4. Cut expenses where you’re not tracking a good R.O.I. Take a closer look at your lead sources—dispense with those that are not producing a solid R.O.I. Don’t ignore this now and risk carrying negative returns into a shifting market.

5. Engage in more coaching. Always be involved in the conversation. Keep up on training, coaching, educational outlets, etc. Your growth depends on it.

For questions related to this list or advice on other real estate-related questions, I’d love to sit and talk with you. Give me a call or email me today!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Boom+or+Bust+in+2019%253F+Be+Ready+for+Either+With+These+5+Steps.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Videos/The+Harrelson+Group+-+Boom+or+Bust+in+2019%253F+Be+Ready+for+Either+With+These+5+Steps.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What kind of growth or turbulence can we expect from the market in 2019? It may not matter to you if you apply these five steps to your own business.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What kind of growth or turbulence can we expect from the market in 2019? It may not matter to you if you apply these five steps to your own business.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Making Connections, Not Just Contacts</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/making-connections-not-just-contacts.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-07-12 10:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Making+Connections.mp4</guid>
        <description>

With all the technology at our disposal, we have never been more disconnected as a society. This is having a real impact on our business as real estate agents. Why are meaningful connections more important than the volume of contacts? What are some ways to deepen the connection with a contact? How can you track your connections and come up with a good metric to measure them? On this episode, we talk about the importance of forming a meaningful connection with people, and how it benefits your business.

“To get business, we have to make true and authentic connections with people. -Greg Harrelson”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Clients are calling back the people they have the strongest connection with.
  The length of time between when you capture a lead and do business with them is a lot longer now, and a real connection will get you through that process.
  Don’t focus on the length of conversations– focus on asking questions.
  Scripts can be very helpful, as they are filled with questions that lead towards genuine connections.


Want to Know Where Greg Harrelson Gets His DATA?Click here: https://www.colerealtyresource.com/landing/realestatesalessolutions/
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Making+Connections.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Making+Connections.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>To get business, we have to make true and authentic connections with people.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>To get business, we have to make true and authentic connections with people.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Tech Companies Can Impact the Future of the Buyer Agent</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-tech-companies-can-impact-the-future-of-the-buyer-agent.html</link>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-17 10:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/impact+the+future.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Technology is causing so many great changes that it can be hard to keep up with it all. What can you do to avoid being negatively affected by shifts in the industry? Is there a threat of our commissions being decreased? What changes might technology bring to buyer’s agents, and how do we adapt to an industry moving so quickly? On this episode, we talk about how agents can prepare themselves for what’s to come.  

“The experience we provide needs to not only be a “wow” experience, but a relevant “wow” experience.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Real estate agents have to learn how to survive when there’s pressure on commissions.
  Right now, it’s better to have a smaller database with high engagement and high connectivity than a large database.
  Our primary value to the market isn’t negotiation– it’s marketing and attracting the right types of buyers.


In the future, real estate agents might make less money, but this does not mean that the consumer is paying less. It means that the piece of the commission pie might get smaller because it’s being distributed amongst additional players. We’re progressing to a point where tech companies will have a bigger stake in real estate. There will constantly be new things coming in from technology companies that will make it easier for consumers, agents and tech companies to justify getting a small piece of the transaction. Agents will have to learn how to thrive when there’s pressure on commissions.

InfusionSoft for real estate. Get up and running fast with our Real Estate Package! 9 pre-built Infusionsoft campaigns, all ready to go.

Connect on Facebook. Follow Greg for more motivational content to take your real estate business to the next level
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/impact+the+future.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/impact+the+future.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The experience we provide needs to not only be a “wow” experience, but a relevant “wow” experience.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The experience we provide needs to not only be a “wow” experience, but a relevant “wow” experience.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Increasing Your Market Share in a Hot Market</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/increasing-your-market-share-in-a-hot-market.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-10 10:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Increasing+Your+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

In a hot market, skilled agents find themselves competing with less skilled agents for clients who may not be able to see the difference right away. How do you prove yourself when the consumer isn’t really looking for skill? Why is a down market actually a lot easier to grow in? How do you go about growing your market share when so many people want a piece of the pie? On this episode, we talk about what it takes to grow your business when the market is up.

“Focus on the systems you have in place and make small tweaks. Then let the compound effect be the reason why you gain market share.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  In a down market the consumer is hiring for skills; But in a hot market they’re just hiring warm bodies.
  There are still plenty of transactions in a down market– there are just fewer agents going after them.
  Don’t reinvent the wheel or focus on shiny objects. Double down on what’s working already.


In a hot market, you get more people with low skill sets flocking to the real estate industry because they think they can make some quick money. In a down market these people leave the business and the skilled agents are in much higher demand. In a hot market, we have more money to buy more shiny objects and open up more circles that we never complete. Those things become distractions that stunt growth. In a down market there are less distractions, and the agents with skill and experience rise to the top, especially when they focus on what works.

Learn more about Infusionsoft for real estate: http://www.realestatesalessolutions.com/
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Increasing+Your+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Increasing+Your+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this episode, we talk about what it takes to grow your business when the market is up.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this episode, we talk about what it takes to grow your business when the market is up.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Self-Leadership</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/self-leadership.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-22 09:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Self-leadership.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’re all leaders because we lead ourselves. Why do you have to be a good self-leader before you’re qualified to lead others effectively? What makes someone a great leader? On this mini-episode, we talk about how to be a better leader, and the secret so few people know about leadership.

“You must be the example for other people to follow.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  You have to be an effective self-leader before you lead others because it gives you credibility.
  If you’re having trouble leading others, you have problems with self-leadership.
  You must be the example for other people to follow.  


A lot of people have a hard time attracting loyal followers because they weren’t followers themselves in the first place. They don’t lead themselves, and that makes it impossible for them to lead others. The truth about leadership is you become better by becoming a great learner, and a great player who follows a great coach. It all starts with you, so ask yourself if you’re a great follower of the things that you say and if you have integrity with the things you tell people do.

Learn more about Infusionsoft for real estate: http://www.realestatesalessolutions.com/
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Self-leadership.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Self-leadership.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this mini-episode, we talk about how to be a better leader, and the secret so few people know about leadership.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this mini-episode, we talk about how to be a better leader, and the secret so few people know about leadership.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Anticipating the Obstacle and Creating the Solution</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/anticipating-the-obstacle-and-creating-the-solution.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-01 09:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Anticipating+the+Obstacles.mp4</guid>
        <description>

This is the time of the year where we evaluate the market for potential risks, and a huge one right now is the risk for low inventory. Why is it so important to plan ahead for these events? How do you fortify yourself from the eventual reduction in inventory? On this episode, we talk about the importance of being ready for potential market risks.

“When I’m already solving a problem that doesn’t yet exist, the problem never appears.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  There’s a lot of quick, easy money on the buyer’s side right now, so people don’t think they need listings.
  If the market continues to rise, sellers are going to slow the pace of houses on the market because they are playing the market for appreciation.
  The two most effective ways to generate leads in a low-inventory environment are expireds and FSBOs.


The goal in business is to always start working a plan as if an upcoming obstacle is there now. You have to set up the systems right now to combat the risks when they do appear. Just because there’s a lot of buying happening right now, don’t fall into the trap of not building up your listings. If inventory to sell runs out, you’re in a better position if you’ve been cultivating listings. Right now, you have a good story to tell sellers in prospecting which is that prices are increasing and inventory is low, so their house could be worth more. That’s a winning script.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Anticipating+the+Obstacles.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Anticipating+the+Obstacles.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>we talk about the importance of being ready for potential market risks.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>we talk about the importance of being ready for potential market risks.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Developing Talent</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/developing-talent.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2018-01-11 10:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Developing+Talent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Developing talent is an important part of going from agent to entrepreneur. How do you connect with your talent on a level that actually resonates with them and their needs? What are the three things we track to make sure what we’re doing is actually working? How do you check in and stay in contact? On this mini-episode, we talk about developing talent, helping people grow and building top producers from scratch.

“Tracking our numbers is going to tell us how we’re doing with our lead generation activities and the conversations we’re having.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  If you can leverage a person’s strengths, you can get to revenue more easily.
  You’ll be able to leverage their strengths faster than you can strengthen their weaknesses.  
  Every transaction is going to come from a conversation.


Most people’s first instinct when it comes to developing talent is to try and get people emotionally invested and fired up by the possibilities they see for that person. What you should actually do first is connect with them on what’s important to them. Honor them by showing that you actually want to know them. When you get into their world you will understand them better. When you do that, their mindset changes, they gain confidence and they become more coachable. This will get you to more income, faster.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Developing+Talent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Developing+Talent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this mini-episode, we talk about developing talent, helping people grow and building top producers from scratch.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this mini-episode, we talk about developing talent, helping people grow and building top producers from scratch.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Eliminate Resistance to Prospecting & Lead Generation</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/how-to-eliminate-resistance-to-prospecting-lead-generation.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2017-11-09 10:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Eliminate+Resistance.mp4</guid>
        <description>

People are looking for a method of lead generation and prospecting that feels comfortable to them. However, this comfort is dictated by bias—not reality. How do you get inspired to make a breakthrough in your resistance to prospecting? Why do people struggle to say they are salespeople? How do you use contribution to get over the monetary motivation? On this episode, we discuss the real reason people resist prospecting and how to overcome it.

“I got over a resistance to prospecting when I changed my perspective.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Contribution goals can be more effective than monetary goals.
  People don’t want to say they are a great salesperson because they associate sales with something bad.
  Change your goal from “how much money you want to make” to how many families you want to help and that will make the job about contribution.


At the start of the show, we talked about why people are always looking for a lead generation method that feels comfortable. Next, we talked about the power of shifting your mindset if you want to get better at lead generation. We also talked about why people don’t want to be associated with being good at sales.

We also discussed:


  How to change your goals from money to contribution
  How to change your perspectives of prospecting activities


It is impossible to successfully overcome hesitation towards prospecting and lead generation without a mindset shift. For most people, the resistance comes from wanting to be comfortable and not wanting to face the limiting beliefs they have about selling. When you change your goals from “make money” to “make a contribution”, you will overcome the fear of being good at selling. When you change your perception of that activity, your comfort level will greatly increase.

Resources

InfusionSoft for real estate. Get up and running fast with our Real Estate Package! 9 pre-built Infusionsoft campaigns, all ready to go.

Connect on Facebook. Follow Greg for more motivational content to take your real estate business to the next level
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Eliminate+Resistance.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Eliminate+Resistance.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this episode, we discuss the real reason people resist prospecting and how to overcome it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this episode, we discuss the real reason people resist prospecting and how to overcome it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Distractions, Momentum & Opportunity: How To Clean Up in a Distracted Market</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/distractions-momentum-opportunity-how-to-clean-up-in-a-distracted-market.html</link>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2017-10-12 11:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Distractions.mp4</guid>
        <description>

With everything happening in the world right now, the consumer is more distracted than ever. How can this cause a shift in momentum in the market? How do you offset the potential losses? How do you bring attention back to what’s important and have the right conversations with your clients? On this episode, we discuss how to maintain momentum, even when people are focused on everything that’s happening in the world.

“When the distraction of the consumer increases, the answer for the agent is to actually decrease distraction and increase their number of contacts.”

Takeaways + Tactics


  There are distractions you can control and distractions you cannot control.
  Right now, the market is so good that it’s even rewarding people who aren’t skilled or efficient.
  Media companies monetize distraction.
  Don’t communicate about the transaction, communicate the motivation.


At the start of the show, we discussed the various things that are distracting the consumer, and what it has to do with the news. Next, we discussed what would go wrong if the both the consumer and the agent are distracted. We also talked about the power of showing people that you really care, and that you want what is best for them. Towards the end of the show, we talked about how people attract business by treating people like they are already your clients.

We also discussed:


  How to get better at asking good questions and listening
  How to increase your activity when the market slows down
  How distraction creates inactivity


Distractions give people a sense of uncertainty. When people feel uncertain, they tend not to make a lot of decisions. If the consumer’s distraction and inaction is coupled with the agent’s inactivity, this can have a huge impact on the market. As an agent, it is your job to limit distractions by having better conversations. In the face of a distractions, keep your client focused on their motivation. Remember: people’s motivation isn’t “to sell a house”, but to acquire the benefits that come along as a result of the sale. If you want to succeed in this distraction-laden market, decrease distraction in your interactions and increase your number of contacts.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Distractions.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Distractions.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On this episode, we discuss how to maintain momentum, even when people are focused on everything that’s happening in the world.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On this episode, we discuss how to maintain momentum, even when people are focused on everything that’s happening in the world.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Art of Relentless Prospecting</title>
        <link>MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com/the-art-of-relentless-prospecting.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Greg Harrelson</author>
        <pubDate>2017-07-13 11:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Relentless+Prospecting.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Many real estate agents prospect for appointments but end up fearing the appointment itself. Why is that? How can we overcome our fear of rejection and make it work for us? Can building a boring day-to-day life really make us successful? In this episode, we reframe rejection and boredom as the key to success.

“If you will go ahead and master the listing presentation first, then you’re excited to make the call”

Takeaways + Tactics


  Agents gravitate toward buyers to avoid rejection and limit their personal growth and their business all at the same time.
  Even when you lose a listing, sellers aren’t rejecting you, they are rejecting your WORDS - something you said during the listing consultation.
  Boredom is about YOU. Change your focus to the people you are serving and you won’t feel boredom.


Resources

InfusionSoft for real estate. Get up and running fast with our Real Estate Package! 9 pre-built Infusionsoft campaigns, all ready to go.

Connect on Facebook. Follow Greg for more motivational content to take your real estate business to the next level

First we talked about building a career out of prospecting and the newfound prospecting generation with real estate agents. We also discussed the benefits of prospecting and its sticking points. Next, we talked about why some people subconsciously avoid prospecting and getting a listing appointment. We agreed that by mastering the listing presentation, then you’ll be less hesitant to get on the phone and get that appointment. We also mentioned how empathy and creating a prospecting ritual can not only benefit the client but also the agent themselves. Finally, we mentioned how appreciation for that style of work grows over time as you get more and more committed to your prospecting ritual.

On this episode we also discussed:


  How failure to follow up can lead to losses
  Overcoming the fear of rejection
  The importance of consistency
  Sustainable boredom and its benefits
  Minimizing distractions through rituals
  and much more


It’s critical to be consistent and persistent at the same time. Rejection is something we will all have to face at some point - so it’s important to reconsider the way we think about being rejected and focus on how to avoid that rejection for the next listing.

And when we talk about consistency, most of the time, boredom has to be a part of the conversation as well. Being boring is now a sustainable choice and a sensible solution for a business. It’s all about installing some variety in your boring day-to-day activities. Mastering that balance and shifting your perspective on rejection and boredom can be a solid way to get more listings and build a successful real estate business.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Relentless+Prospecting.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="MyrtleBeachRealEstateMastermind.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Greg+Harrelson/Recruiting/Relentless+Prospecting.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>In this episode, we reframe rejection and boredom as the key to success.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Greg Harrelson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>In this episode, we reframe rejection and boredom as the key to success.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Myrtle Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Greg Harrelson</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Greg Harrelson</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Harrelson Group - your professional Myrtle Beach Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
